

Samer Bahri

DevOps Engineer Budapest/Hungary

+36 20 433 6216 | samer.bahri@ieee.org

🗘 /samerbahri98 | in /in/samerbahri

Summary _

I am a Tunisian DevOps Engineer based in Hungary, with 3 years of experience specializing in platform engineering, MLOps, cloud, and DevOps practices. I hold a BSc in Software Engineering from the Budapest University of Technology and Economics. Passionate about innovation, I actively engage in homelabbing and open-source contributions to refine my skills and explore emerging technologies.

Experience _

DevOps Engineer | Ericsson

2023-Current/Hungary

- Handled responsabilities related to Kubernetes, CI/CD and Cloud Object Storage (MinIO S3) for Packet Core and Application Development Platform
- Took over responsabilities related to a Kubernetes microservice architecture, design and implementation details
- Refactored the testing framework for a Kubernetes microservice
- Was a spoc for different technical stakeholders
- Was a deputee for the scrum master and the product owner during absences

Software Engineering Intern | Continental AG

2022-2023 / Hungary

- Implemented features and bug fixes as well as CI/CD for an internal web application (abstraction over kubernetes)
- Took part in Infrastructure and DevOps/MLOps improvements for the AI training cluster

Customer Care Intern | Suez

2019-2020 / Hungary

- Handled SalesForce and SAP customer success cases
- Automated invoice email sending with python

Contributions _____

- Implemented the backup and restore feature in Ansible Semaphore 🔾
- Created a Middleware Plugin for Traefik to sign http requests with AWS credentials 🗘 😵
- Fixed a minor bug in Vultr Ansible Collection 🔾

Projects ____

- Breen | An MLOps platform on Kubernetes 🗘
- SCM | A Git Repository Manager 🗘
- Vault | A password manager 🕠

Education and Certifications _

BSc in Computer Engineering

January 2023

BUDAPEST UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY AND ECONOMICS

Certified Kubernetes Application Developer (CKAD)

October 2023

THE LINUX FOUNDATION

Fundamentals of Deep Learning

April 2022

NVIDIA

Skills _____

Programming Languages Python | Typescript | Javascript | Go

Bash | GIT | GitHub | Jenkins | GNU Make | pnpm | vite Software Development Cloud Technologies Docker | Kubernetes | Helm | AWS | Terraform | Ansible

Frameworks & Libraries React | Express | Flask | Robot Framework | Pytest | Tensorflow

> Soft Skills Project Management | Cross-team coordination | Agile Methodologies | Presentations

Languages Native: Arabic Fluent: English, French Beginner: Swedish

December 17, 2024 / source code